hirebridge.com 2018-03-09

# Hirebridge Applicant Tracking Solutions :: Privacy Policy

**Hirebridge is committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.  **

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Hirebridge's Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. 

If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information to us via our website, we may transfer that Information within Hirebridge or to Hirebridge's third-party service providers, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. 

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies  
**Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.   
You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web site. Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.

**Notice  
**Where Hirebridge collects Personal Information on via our website, we intend to post a purpose statement that explains why Personal Information will be collected. Hirebridge does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Hirebridge behalf unless such transfer is legally required. 

**Choice  
**You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Hirebridge. The notice we intend to provide where Hirebridge collects Personal Information on the Web should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of Hirebridge Web sites, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you. If you chose to have a relationship with Hirebridge such as a contractual or other business relationship or partnership, we will naturally continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship. 

**Security  
**Wherever your Personal Information may be held within Hirebridge or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. 

**Access/Accuracy  
**To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Hirebridge wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting Hirebridge should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to [privacy@Hirebridge.com ](mailto:privacy@Hirebridge.com)and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable. 

**Third Party Services  
**Third parties provide certain services available on Hirebridge.com on Hirebridge's behalf. Hirebridge may provide information, including Personal Information, that Hirebridge collects on the Web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which Hirebridge maintains its Web site and mailing lists. Hirebridge will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on Hirebridge's behalf. 

Hirebridge does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Hirebridge's behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against Hirebridge's policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent. 

**Children's Privacy  
**Hirebridge.com is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. 

**Questions and Comments  
**We are committed to maintaining your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Hirebridge's Web sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@hirebridge.com](mailto:privacy@hirebridge.com). 

**Your Consent  
**By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Hirebridge's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where Hirebridge collects Personal Information on the Web. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.

Hirebridge complies with the EU – U.S. Privacy Shield Framework (the “Privacy Shield”) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield principles, the Privacy Shield principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov.](https://www.privacyshield.gov./)

[The Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) of Canada](https://www.priv.gc.ca/information/pub/guide_ind_e.asp)  
Hirebridge complies with The Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) set forth by the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada which details the rules for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information in the course of commercial activity as defined by the Act. 

To learn more about PIPEDA, please visit <https://www.priv.gc.ca/information/pub/guide_ind_e.asp>.

If you have questions about PIPEDA as it pertains to the use or storage of, and access to your personal information, please contact us at [privacy@hirebridge.com](mailto:privacy@hirebridge.com)

* * *

Have questions about Hirebridge's applicant tracking software or hiring management solutions? Visit our Features Page or give us a call at 1-954-906-5727. We are here to help.

Our [free trial account](http://www.hirebridge.com/corp/demo_form.asp) gives you plenty of time to get familiar with the powerful features available with Hirebridge Recruiter. It's risk free. No credit card required. Sign up today!
